{
    "id": "798bc5a086a046bcbfd709a844acde6c",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There ………………………….. a famine in Bengal in",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished actions and situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce560a09b7cf4670b5573a38c2f5be06"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gandhi …………………………… in the principle of non-violence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "believed",
                "has believed",
                "believes"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f02fa12af83c4c7087a13a914dd4ef62"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have not …………………………. yet.",
            "description": "We use a past participle form after has, have and had.",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "arriving",
                "arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "74f589b81fe24971a82cac5ef26ddbd8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… not want to quit her job.",
            "description": "We make questions and negatives in the simple present tense with do and does. We use does with singular nouns and pronouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "38fc9a6ff87b4b78ac0d78ddc7253a5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ozone layer ……………………………… us from harmful ultraviolet radiations.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "protect",
                "protects",
                "is protecting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56d0a862c13249ba94c723053524a9a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………… her studies before she went abroad.",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of two past actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "completed",
                "has completed",
                "had completed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bfdcd53785334a5bb96a350831b9b218"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. him on several occasions before he went to America.",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of two past actions or situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "93a857a505e4409899a9790102f6c7d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jenny …………………………….. alone in her apartment.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "is living"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b82357cfac9a4a7f9bab32c534a1559b"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was young, I …………………………… every day.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about past habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "worked out",
                "was working out",
                "had worked out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a850cb58352f4cffb5ea5281f3e1d07d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………………. for Malaysia tonight.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about pre-planned future events. ",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "will leave",
                "are leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "961f7c35ac304648bdc827bf6a441d4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Barking dogs seldom …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bite",
                "will bite",
                "would bite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cbd3793639ad48e09fd4c53876c64473"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you ………………………………. him yesterday?",
            "description": "We use the first form of the verb after do, does and did.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "saw",
                "seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5c6073f339a24ec191665e38ad696682"
        }
    ]
}